### Personal details

Name: Joey ter Meulen

Address: Förskottsvägen 11 - 1001 12932 Stockholm, Sweden

Phone: 0046 720101196

E-mail: joeytermeulen@gmail.com

Date of birth: 16-02-1989

Nationality: Dutch

### **Overview**

Hello! I am Joey, a 31-year-old frontend web developer from Amsterdam, the Netherlands. In 2017 I discovered coding and after extensive home studies, I officially joined the development industry at the start of 2018. I have since been professionally developing websites, focusing on React.js, Node.js and GraphQI.

With 3 years of working experience, React.js is my main strength - but in my spare time, Unity and C# take over. Coding games is just as fun!

I will soon be moving to Barcelona after living in Stockholm, Sweden for the past four years. I'm looking for a fresh new challenge at a company that champions their team spirit as much as their product. I enjoy working with other crafts, collaborating daily with UI/UX, QA and backend developers. I'm always open to feedback and new ideas and can handle stress very well. I am organised, make quick decisions and I can lead a group when I need to.

# Job experience

April 2018 current **LeoVegas** Luntmakargatan 18, 111 37 Stockholm, Sweden

**Occupation:** Frontend WebDeveloper (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

**Job description:** LeoVegas is an online casino provider. My daily job includes developing

new features, especially to enhance the game experience for players. I work with React.js, Node.js and GraphQl on a daily basis. Other responsibilities include writing tests for the features we develop, maintain and bug-fix any feature previously released, and close collaboration between designers and

BackEnd developers.

September 2016 -January 2018 **Swagg** Elektravägen 5, 126 30 Hägersten, Sweden

**Occupation:** Textile printer (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

**Job description:** Manually and mechanically printing of textile, starting with

digitally designing and preparing the printing process, all the way to the

printing itself.

July 2015 -July 2016 **Expeditors** Ganderweg 1, 1118 LH, Schiphol, Netherlands

**Occupation**: Warehouse employee (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

**Job description**: Breaking down freight from plates by hand and with a

forklift, unloading and loading trucks with pallets and packages. Scanning

and storing the freight in the warehouse.

January 2009 -July 2015 **Refero** Kollenbergweg 78B, 1101 AV, Amsterdam, Netherlands

**Occupation:** Textile printer, manager (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

**Job description:** Manually and mechanically printing of textile, starting with

digitally designing and preparing the printing process, all the way to the printing itself. I was also responsible for planning and managing the

workfloor.

January 2008 -January 209 **Schiphol Airport** employment agency Content, Amsterdam, Netherlands

**Occupation:** Flight Ramp agent (36 hours a week)

**Job description:** Loading and unloading cargo and baggage on and off

airplanes.

Through internal courses, my responsibilities extended to docking

incoming airplanes.

### Skills

Javascript	
React.js	••••••
HTML5	••••••
CSS	••••••
Redux	•••••••
Node.js	••••••
Express	••••••000
C# / Unity	●●●●○○○○
Python	●●●●●○○○○

## **Education and Courses**

2020	CodeWithMosh - <u>Java Mastery Series</u>
2020	Udemy - Node.JS Advanced Course
2019	Udemy - Unity 2D Game Dev Course
2019	Udemy - <u>Unreal Engine Game Dev Course</u>
2018	Udemy - ECMAScript 6 Course

2018 Udemy - React Complete Guide

2017 Udemy - <u>Advanced Web Developer Bootcamp</u>

2017 **Udemy - Web Developer Bootcamp** 

2017 LearnCodeTheHardWay - Book on the principles of coding in Python

2007-2008 InHolland - HBO Commercial Economics 2001-2007 Calandlyceum Amsterdam - HAVO Graduated